[
    {"question": "🇧🇴", "response": "Bolivia" }, 
    {"question": "🇵🇪", "response": "Peru" }, 
    {"question": "🇦🇷", "response": "Argentina" }, 
    {"question": "🇦🇺", "response": "Australia" }, 
    {"question": "🇪🇦", "response": "España" }, 
    {"question": "🇨🇦", "response": "Canadá" }, 
    {"question": "🇩🇪", "response": "Alemania" }, 
    {"question": "🇵🇹", "response": "Portugal" }, 
    {"question": "🇷🇺", "response": "Rusia" }, 
    {"question": "🇨🇱", "response": "Chile" }, 
    {"question": "🇬🇹", "response": "Guatemala" }, 
    {"question": "🇨🇳", "response": "China" }, 
    {"question": "🇯🇵", "response": "Japón" }, 
    {"question": "🇩🇪", "response": "Alemania" },
    {"question": "🇨🇺", "response": "Cuba" }, 
    {"question": "🇵🇷", "response": "Puerto Rico" }, 
    {"question": "🇧🇷", "response": "Brasil" }, 
    {"question": "🇺🇦", "response": "Ucrania" }, 
    {"question": "🇵🇦", "response": "Panamá" }, 
    {"question": "🇮🇹", "response": "Italia" }, 
    {"question": "🇪🇨", "response": "Ecuador" }, 
    {"question": "🇻🇪", "response": "Venezuela" }, 
    {"question": "🇨🇴", "response": "Colombia" }, 
    {"question": "🇲🇽", "response": "México" }, 
    {"question": "🇮🇳", "response": "India" }, 
    {"question": "🇵🇾", "response": "Paraguay" }
    ]